// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which among the compounds has the strongest intermolecular forces and ionic crystal?",
    answer: "C. salt",
    options: [
      "A. quartz",
      "B. rubber",
      "C. salt",
      "D. sugar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which among the compounds has covalent crystals with a very high melting point?",
    answer: "A. quartz",
    options: [
      "A. quartz",
      "B. rubber",
      "C. salt",
      "D. sugar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which among the compounds is an amorphous solid with no sharp melting points?",
    answer: "B. rubber",
    options: [
      "A. quartz",
      "B. rubber",
      "C. salt",
      "D. sugar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following classes of solids does not have a well-defined geometric pattern?",
    answer: "A. amorphous solids",
    options: [
      "A. amorphous solids",
      "B. crystalline solids",
      "C. ionic crystalline solids",
      "D. molecular crystalline solids"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is the basic repeating structural unit of crystalline solids?",
    answer: "D. unit cell",
    options: [
      "A. atom",
      "B. compound",
      "C. molecule",
      "D. unit cell"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is an amorphous solid that can convert sunlight into electrical energy?",
    answer: "D. silicon",
    options: [
      "A. glass",
      "B. plastics",
      "C. rubber",
      "D. silicon"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following best describes the melting point of amorphous solid?",
    answer: "C. Amorphous solids do not have sharp melting points since they have a weak intermolecular force",
    options: [
      "A. Amorphous solids have definite melting points since they have a weak intermolecular force",
      "B. Amorphous solids have definite melting points since they have a strong intermolecular force",
      "C. Amorphous solids do not have sharp melting points since they have a weak intermolecular force",
      "D. Amorphous solids do not have a sharp melting point since they have strong intermolecular forces"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Why does crystalline solids considered as true solids?",
    answer: "D. because of its sharp melting point that once it reaches this point it will immediately change into liquid form",
    options: [
      "A. because of their repeated pattern of arrangement",
      "B. because that can be molded and blown into various shapes",
      "C. because they behave as crystalline at a certain temperature",
      "D. because of its sharp melting point that once it reaches this point it will immediately change into liquid form"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Why does the solid-state and molten state of ionic crystals considered poor electrical conductors?",
    answer: "C. because their particles are held firmly thus there is no enough space for the ions to move around which make them as non-conductors of electricity",
    options: [
      "A. because of delocalized electrons that can freely room across the entire metal",
      "B. because they have a definite heat of fusion that help them to change their phase",
      "C. because their particles are held firmly thus there is no enough space for the ions to move around which make them as non-conductors of electricity",
      "D. because their particles are NOT held firmly thus there is no enough space for the ions to move around which make them as non-conductors of electricity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following solids describes a crystalline solid? ",
    answer: "A. They are composed of a huge number of small crystals with a definite geometrical shape making them rigid and incompressible",
    options: [
      "A. They are composed of a huge number of small crystals with a definite geometrical shape making them rigid and incompressible",
      "B. They are composed of a huge number of small crystals with no definite geometrical shape making them rigid and incompressible",
      "C. They are composed of a huge number of small crystals with indefinite. geometrical shapes making them rigid and incompressible",
      "D. They are composed of a huge number of small crystals with a definite geometrical shape making them rigid and highly compressible"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];